OKAY, THIS IS IT.
YOU SURE YOU WANT
TO DO THIS?
( laughing )
HELLO, MRS. ROSS!
WHY, HELLO, MR. RACHEL!
WHOA!
OH, MY GOD.
( rapid footsteps )
HURRY! HURRY! HURRY UP!
YEAH, YEAH, OKAY.
HURRY! HURRY!
OH, MY GOD!
IS EVERYBODY GETTING MARRIED?!
NO RUNNING IN THE CHAPEL.
HEY, DON'T YOU GIVE ME
ANY OF YOUR...
HEY!
HEY.
HEY, WHAT ARE
YOU GUYS DOING HERE?
ROSS AND RACHEL
LEFT US A MESSAGE
SAYING THEY WERE
GETTING MARRIED.
ISN'T THAT WHY
YOU GUYS ARE HERE?
YES. WELL, YES...
WHY ELSE WOULD
WE BE HERE?
WELL, WHAT HAPPENED?
DID WE MISS IT?
WE ACTUALLY MISSED IT.
WELL, MAYBE YOU WOULDN'T HAVE
IF YOU COULD RUN
IN THE CHAPEL!
THIS IS INSANE.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT LIKE
IT'S A REAL MARRIAGE.
WHAT?
IF YOU GET MARRIED IN VEGAS,
YOU'RE ONLY MARRIED IN VEGAS.
Monica:
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
IF YOU GET MARRIED
IN VEGAS, YOU'RE
MARRIED EVERYWHERE.
REALLY?
YEAH.
OH, MY GOD.
EH, WELL.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
( clattering )
HMM...
OH.
( groans )
( gasps )
( both screaming )
WHY ARE WE IN
BED TOGETHER?
I DON'T KNOW.
DO YOU...
DO YOU HAVE
ANY CLOTHES ON?
YES.
REALLY?
NO.
BUT WE DIDN'T HAVE...
SEX, DID WE?
I DON'T...
I DON'T REMEMBER MUCH
ABOUT LAST NIGHT.
IT WAS SUCH A BLUR.
OH!
I REMEMBER LAUGHING.
I LAUGHED A LOT.
THEN WE DIDN'T
HAVE SEX.
( groans )
OH, I MEAN, WE WERE
REALLY DRUNK.
I'M GLAD WE DIDN'T
DO ANYTHING STUPID.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
MORNING, PHEEBS.
HEY.
WELL, MY MOVIE HAS BEEN
OFFICIALLY CANCELED.
JOEY, I'M SO SORRY.
YOU WANT SOME
OF MY BREAKFAST?
NAH. I'M TOO
DEPRESSED TO EAT.
I'LL PROBABLY BE EATING
IN, LIKE, FIVE MINUTES.
SO I GUESS I'LL JUST
FLY HOME WITH YOU GUYS.
WHAT TIME'S YOUR FLIGHT?
WHAT ABOUT MY CAB?
I DON'T NEED THAT ANYMORE.
NO, JOEY, YOU
BORROWED MY CAB.
YOU HAVE TO DRIVE IT BACK.
I DON'T WANT TO DRIVE
ALL THE WAY BACK BY MYSELF.
I GET SO LONELY.
OH, OH, HOW ABOUT
IF YOU COME WITH ME?
I DON'T KNOW, IT'S
SUCH A LONG TRIP.
IT'LL BE GREAT.
WE CAN TALK
AND PLAY GAMES, HUH?
THIS COULD BE OUR CHANCE
TO, LIKE, RENEW OUR FRIENDSHIP.
ARE YOU ASKING
ME TO HAVE A
FRIEND-AISSANCE?
SURE?
ALL RIGHT.
ALTHOUGH I DON'T THINK
WE REALLY NEED ONE, BABY.
I NEVER STOPPED LOVIN' YOU.
HEY.
Joey:
SO HAS ANYBODY TALKED
TO DR. AND MRS. GELLER YET?
MM-HMM. YEAH.
THEY LEFT ME A MESSAGE.
THEY SHOULD BE HERE
ANY MINUTE.
WHERE IS THE WAITRESS?
I'M STARVING.
IT'S A BUFFET, MAN.
OH, HERE'S WHERE I WIN
ALL MY MONEY BACK.
LISTEN, I GOT
TO TALK TO YOU.
SURE. WHAT'S UP?
MONICA AND I ALMOST
GOT MARRIED LAST NIGHT.
OH, MY GOD!
THAT'S HUGE!
HEY!
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHY WASN'T I INVITED?
AND WHO WAS
GOING TO BE
YOUR BEST MAN?
DON'T SAY ROSS.
DO NOT SAY ROSS.
LOOK, I JUST DON'T THINK
THAT MONICA AND I
ARE READY TO GET MARRIED
YET, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, I LOVE HER
AND EVERYTHING, BUT...
SEEING ROSS AND RACHEL
COMING OUT OF THAT CHAPEL
WAS LIKE A... LIKE
A WAKE-UP CALL
THAT MONICA AND I ARE
MOVING SO FAST, YOU KNOW.
HOW DO I TELL HER
WITHOUT CRUSHING HER?
OH.
TELL HER SHE'S NOT
MARRIAGE MATERIAL.
WHAT?
GIRLS SAY IT TO ME
ALL THE TIME.
AND BELIEVE ME
IF SHE'S ANYTHING
LIKE ME
SHE'S JUST GOING
TO BE RELIEVED.
HOW DO I TELL CHANDLER
THAT IT'S TOO SOON?
IT'S GOING
TO BREAK HIS HEART.
HE'S GOING TO THINK
I DON'T LOVE HIM ANYMORE.
WELL, YOU DON'T.
YES, I DO.
WELL, GOOD, GOOD.
I WAS JUST TESTING YOU.
Chandler:
HI.
OH, HI, HI.
YOU KNOW, WE WERE JUST
TALKING ABOUT BACON.
NO, WE WERE TALKING
ABOUT TENNIS.
TENNIS IS MORE BELIEVABLE.
HEY.
HI.
THANK YOU.
MM.
WHAT?
ARE WE GOING
TO TALK ABOUT
WHAT YOU GUYS
DID LAST NIGHT, OR...?
WHAT... WHAT DO YOU
MEAN LAST NIGHT?
NOTHING-NOTHING...
NOTHING HAPPENED
LAST NIGHT.
YEAH.
UH-HUH.
ROSS INVITED US
ALL TO WATCH.
RACH, WE WEREN'T
GOING TO MISS
OUR FRIENDS
GETTING MARRIED.
( gasps ):
WHO GOT MARRIED?!
YOU DID?
WHAT?
WE... WE... HELLO?
NO, WE DIDN'T.
WE DIDN'T GET MARRIED.
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
( both gasp )
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
I REMEMBER BEING
IN A CHAPEL.
THEY WOULD NOT LET
US GET MARRIED
WHEN WE WERE
THAT DRUNK.
THEY LET YOU GET MARRIED
WHEN YOU'RE DRUNK.
MOST PEOPLE GETTING MARRIED
IN VEGAS ARE DRUNK.
I'M DRUNK
RIGHT NOW.
WHAT, I CAN'T HAVE
A MIMOSA WITH BREAKFAST?
I'M ON
VACATION.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
GOING TO DO?
I GUESS WE JUST FIND
A DIVORCE LAWYER?
WELL, I THINK...
I THINK ROSS
ALREADY HAS ONE.
THIS ONE'S FREE, RIGHT?
BECAUSE YOU PAID
FOR THE FIRST TWO
SO YOU GET THE THIRD ONE
FOR FREE.
LAUGH IT UP.
BUT THE JOKE'S
ON YOU.
BECAUSE WE DON'T NEED
TO GET DIVORCED, OKAY?
WE'RE JUST GOING
TO GET AN ANNULMENT.
Joey:
AN ANNULMENT?
ROSS, I DON'T THINK
SURGERY'S THE ANSWER HERE.
OH, THAT'S
YOUR THING.
WHAT?
YOUR THING,
YOUR THING, YOU KNOW.
YOU'RE THE GUY
WHO GETS DIVORCED.
OH, YEAH.
IT MIGHT
BE TRUE.
IT'S NOT
MY "THING."
I DO NOT LOVE
GETTING DIVORCED.
YES, YOU DO.
THIS IS YOUR
THIRD DIVORCE.
GOD, YOU LOVE
DIVORCE SO MUCH
YOU'RE PROBABLY
GOING TO MARRY IT
AND THEN...
AND THEN IT WON'T WORK OUT
SO YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO DIVORCE IT, DIVORCING GUY.
( laughing )
I'M SO DRUNK.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD DO?
I DON'T KNOW.
I-I-I KNOW I LOVE YOU.
I KNOW I LOVE YOU.
SO WHERE ARE WE
ON THE WHOLE
GOING-BACK-TO-THE-PLACE-
WHERE-THEY-HAVE-ALL-
THE-MARRIAGES THING?
I LOVE YOU.
THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION.
WELL, LAST NIGHT WE
LET THE DICE DECIDE.
MAYBE WE SHOULD LEAVE
IT UP TO FATE AGAIN.
I LOVE YOU.
YES, WE DON'T GET MARRIED
UNLESS THERE'S A SIGN, OKAY?
SO, SAY... SAY YOU ROLL
ANOTHER EIGHT
THEN THERE IS
A DEFINITE SIGN
THAT WE SHOULD GET MARRIED.
ALL RIGHT, EIGHT,
WE GET MARRIED
BUT TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE,
SIX, SEVEN, NINE, 10, 11, 12
WE DON'T GET MARRIED.
SOUNDS GREAT.
OKAY.
OKAY, WE GOT
A SHOOTER.
MONEY, PLEASE.
YOU READY?
READY.
COME ON, EIGHT.
YES, YES, EIGHT.
Man:
EIGHT, EASY EIGHT.
WOW, I CAN'T BELIEVE I
ACTUALLY ROLLED AN EIGHT.
THAT WAS SO UNLIKELY.
WELL, LET'S GET MARRIED...
I GUESS.
THAT WASN'T
A HARD EIGHT.
LAST NIGHT I ROLLED
THAT'S RIGHT, IT WAS
THE WRONG KIND OF EIGHT.
NO WEDDING! DAMN IT!
( both groaning )
I WANTED IT SO BAD.
WANT TO GO PACK?
YEAH.
WE'RE DOING THE
RIGHT THING, RIGHT?
OF COURSE WE ARE.
WE LEFT IT UP
TO FATE.
IF WE WERE SUPPOSED
TO GET MARRIED
THERE WOULD BE
A CLEAR-CUT SIGN.
OKAY, YOU HAVE
19 QUESTIONS LEFT.
USE THEM WISELY.
( mumbles )
COME ON, JOEY,
YOU CAN'T WIN
IF YOU DON'T ASK ANY...
( shouts ):
QUESTIONS!
I'M UP! WHAT?!
WHAT?
WELL, YOU PROMISED ME
A FUN ROAD TRIP
AND WE'VE BEEN ON
THE ROAD FOR SIX HOURS
AND YOU'VE BEEN ASLEEP
FOR FIVE AND A HALF.
WE ARE SWITCHING
AT THE NEXT REST STOP
AND YOU ARE
GOING TO DRIVE
THE WHOLE WAY BACK.
THAT WILL BE
YOUR PUNISHMENT
YOU GREEDY SLEEPER.
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
AND UNTIL THEN,
YOU ARE GOING
TO SING TO ME.
BECAUSE THE
RADIO'S BROKEN
AND YOU ARE SELFISH...
BUT YOU HAVE
A NICE VOICE.
REALLY? I DON'T...
SING!
♪ I WANNA ROCK 'N' ROLL
ALL NIGHT... ♪
Joey:
MAN, THIS IS A LONG DRIVE.
ARE MY EYES OPEN?
NO!
( screams )
GOOD MORNING.
HEY.
HEY, HUBBY.
( laughing )
ACTUALLY, UM, I WANTED
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT
THAT WHOLE
ANNULMENT THING.
UH-HUH?
YEAH, I'M NOT
GOING TO DO THAT.
( both laughing )
OKAY!
SO... WE'LL JUST
STAY MARRIED.
YES, EXACTLY.
AND I WILL MAKE EVERYONE
CALL ME MRS. GELLER.
WOW, THIS IS SO AMAZING.
I, UH...
I REALLY THOUGHT I'D HAVE
TO TALK YOU INTO THIS MORE.
OKAY, SEE, NOW I'M SCARED
BECAUSE I DON'T ACTUALLY
THINK YOU'RE KIDDING.
I'M-I'M NOT KIDDING.
LOOK, I-I...
I CAN'T HAVE THREE
FAILED MARRIAGES.
I CAN'T, OKAY?
I-I-I AM NOT GOING
TO BE THAT GUY.
WHAT? WELL, WH-WHAT...
SO... SO, WHAT, WE JUST
STAY MARRIED FOREVER?
HOW-HOW IS THIS GOING
TO AFFECT YOU, REALLY?
I MEAN, YOU FILL SOME FORM
OUT ONCE IN A WHILE.
INSTEAD OF CHECKING
THE BOX THAT SAYS "MISS"
YOU CHECK THE BOX
THAT SAYS "MRS."
IT'S RIGHT NEXT TO IT.
OH, OKAY, I'M SORRY,
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU KNOW WHAT? WE ABSOLUTELY
CAN STAY MARRIED
BECAUSE I WAS UNDER
THE IMPRESSION
THAT THE BOXES WERE
FAR AWAY FROM EACH OTHER.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, JUST...
PLEASE, TAKE A MOMENT HERE
AND THINK ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE
ASKING OF ME, OKAY?
I AM ASKING YOU
TO DO ME A FAVOR.
YOU ARE ASKING ME
TO BE YOUR WIFE.
AND AS MY WIFE,
I THINK YOU SHOULD
GRANT ME THIS FAVOR.
THAT KID KICKED ME
REALLY HARD ON THE PLANE.
WELL, YOU DID PULL HIS HAIR.
HE TOOK MY SNACK.
I'M NOT GETTING
INTO THIS AGAIN!
OKAY!
OH, GOD, YOU
KNOW WHAT?
IT HURTS REALLY BAD.
WELL, I TOLD YOU
NOT TO WALK...
HERE. HERE.
OKAY.
THIS DOESN'T
MEAN ANYTHING, DOES IT?
NO.
OKAY.
HOW COULD
YOU PICK UP
A HITCHHIKER?
HE COULD BE A RAP...
HE COULD BE A RAPIST OR
A KILLER OR SOMETHING.
DON'T YOU THINK I ASKED HIM THAT
BEFORE HE GOT IN?
YOU KNOW WHAT? I'M
NOT TALKING TO YOU.
YOU GO BACK TO
SLEEP. AND YOU--
ARE YOU A RAPIST?
NO.
DO YOU LIKE
CAR GAMES?
YEAH. YOU KNOW,
THE, UH, LICENSE PLATE GAME?
I LOVE THE LICENSE
PLATE GAME.
OH, I'LL PLAY.
I'LL PLAY.
NO, NO. YOU NEED
YOUR SLEEP.
NIGHT NIGHT.
SHH.
HEY.
LISTEN.
I KNOW YOU WANTED
TO TALK TO ME
BUT I HAVE AN IDEA
THAT MAY MAKE YOU
WANT TO STAY MARRIED.
WE REGISTER, AND YOU GET
TO KEEP ALL THE PRESENTS.
NO.
ROSS, COME ON.
NO. LISTEN. LOOK,
I'VE THOUGHT A LOT
ABOUT HOW TO TELL
YOU THIS AND, UM...
THE BOTTOM LINE, ROSS,
IS WE CANNOT STAY MARRIED.
I DON'T KNOW IF THAT'S TRUE.
BUT IT-IT-IT IS.
OKAY, YOU KNOW
WHAT THIS IS?
THIS IS A DIFFERENCE
OF OPINION.
AND WHEN THAT HAPPENS
IN A MARRIAGE...
OH, ROSS, COME ON!
THIS IS NOT A...
THIS IS NOT A MARRIAGE.
THIS IS THE WORLD'S
WORST HANGOVER!
ROSS, LISTEN
IF YOU DO NOT GET
THIS ANNULMENT, I WILL.
ALL RIGHT.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL DO IT.
THANK YOU.
HEY-HEY, UM...
UH, IS THERE
ANY SUCH THING
AS AN ANNULMENT SHOWER?
Man:
OH, WAIT, WAIT.
THERE'S THE TRAIN STATION.
THIS IS WHERE
I GET OFF.
I HAVE YOUR ADDRESS
AND PHONE NUMBER.
AND I HAVE YOUR NAME
AND THE FACT THAT
YOU'RE A DRIFTER, SO...
BALL'S PRETTY MUCH
IN YOUR COURT.
ALL RIGHT
SEE YOU, PHEEBS.
COME ON, PHEEBS.
I CAN'T TAKE THIS
ANYMORE.
PLEASE TALK TO ME.
LET-LET ME MAKE IT
UP TO YOU, HUH?
♪ GROUND CONTROL TO MAJOR TOM ♪
♪ COMMENCING COUNTDOWN,
ENGINES ON ♪
♪ TAKE YOUR PROTEIN PILLS
AND PUT YOUR HELMET ON ♪
( makes buzzing noise )
STOP IT!
♪ THIS IS GROUND... ♪
STOP IT! NO!
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
YOU KNOW I CAN'T RESIST
THAT BEAUTIFUL VOICE.
PHEEBS, LOOK,
I'M SO SORRY.
I KNOW I PROMISED YOU
A FUN ROAD TRIP WITH YOUR FRIEND
AND I DIDN'T DELIVER, OKAY,
BUT-BUT-BUT NOW I KNOW
THAT YOU THINK BEING AWAKE
IS AN IMPORTANT PART
OF FRIENDSHIP, SO...
SO...
SO I WILL STRIVE
TO-TO STAY AWAKE
FOR AS LONG AS I KNOW YOU.
YOU CAN STILL, LIKE,
SLEEP AT NIGHT AND STUFF.
WELL, THANK YOU.
SO, CAN WE PLAY
20 QUESTIONS NOW?
I GOT A REALLY GOOD ONE.
I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT IT
SINCE KANSAS.
OKAY.
IS IT... A KIND
OF HOT SANDWICH?
YES.
IS IT A MEATBALL SUB?
THAT IS INCREDIBLE.
YOU ARE THE MASTER.
( shrieking ):
BUG!
THAT'S FUNNY.
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE
GOING TO BE THE NEXT ONE...
DON'T SAY IT.
DON'T EVEN THINK IT.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, CHANDLER,
ENJOY YOUR HANDFUL.
ALL RIGHT,
SHOULD WE JUST...
SHOULD WE JUST
GET MARRIED, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, SHOULD WE
JUST DO IT?
ALL THE SIGNS
ARE TELLING US
TO DO IT.
I'M SICK OF THE SIGNS.
IT'S TOO FAST.
I'M HAPPY THE WAY THINGS ARE.
ME, TOO.
I DON'T WANT THINGS TO CHANGE;
DO YOU?
NO.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
THEN NOTHING CHANGES!
EVERYTHING IS GREAT!
EVERYTHING STAYS THE SAME!
NOW, YOU GO AND UNPACK
'CAUSE IT'S BEEN THREE DAYS
AND IT'S DRIVING
ME INSANE.
AH, GEEZ, RELAX.
IT'S NOT LIKE WE'RE MA...
AH! AH!
( door shuts )
YOU KNOW, I WAS THINKING,
WHAT IF I, UH, UNPACK HERE?
THEN ALL YOUR STUFF
WOULD BE HERE.
WELL...
WHAT IF ALL MY STUFF WAS HERE?
THEN YOU'D BE GOING
BACK AND FORTH ALL THE TIME.
I MEAN...
DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
OKAY.
WHAT IF WE LIVE TOGETHER
AND YOU UNDERSTAND
WHAT I'M SAYING?
LIVE TOGETHER?
THERE HAVE BEEN
NO SIGNS FOR THAT.
ME ASKING IS KIND OF A SIGN.
YES!
OKAY!
YES. OKAY.
OKAY, WAIT.
WAIT. WAIT. WAIT.
OKAY.
HERE'S YOUR KEY.
ALL RIGHT, NOW, YOU HAVE
TO GO OUT AND CHRISTEN IT.
NOW, GO OUT AND THEN
COME BACK IN.
THE DOOR HASN'T BEEN LOCKED
IN FIVE YEARS, BUT OKAY.
READY?
READY!
OKAY, A LITTLE
PROBLEM.
THE KEY BROKE IN THE LOCK
AND I CAN'T GET IN.
OH, MY GOD. I CAN'T GET OUT.
THIS ISN'T A SIGN.
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S NOT A SIGN.
IT'S A VERY OLD KEY.
IT'S JUST AN OLD KEY!
OH, MY GOD. IT'S OLD.
I LOVE YOU.
ARE YOU HUGGING
THE DOOR RIGHT NOW?
NO.
YEAH, YEAH.
ME, NEITHER.
HEY.
HEY. SO, DID EVERYTHING
GO ALL RIGHT
WITH THE, UH, ANNULMENT?
OH, YEAH.
NO PROBLEMS. IT'S
ALL TAKEN CARE OF.
ROSS, THANK YOU.
AAH...
HEY, DO YOU GUYS
WANT TO GO SEE A MOVIE?
OH, YEAH. WHY NOT?
YEAH. PHEEBS?
NO, THANKS.
I'VE ALREADY SEEN ONE.
OKAY. UM...
I'LL GET MY SWEATER.
OKAY.
YOU WANT-YOU
WANT TO HEAR
SOMETHING WEIRD?
ALWAYS.
I DIDN'T GET THE ANNULMENT.
WHAT?
WE'RE STILL MARRIED.
DON'T TELL RACHEL.
SEE YOU LATER.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
KEY'S STUCK IN THE LOCK.
I CAN FIX IT.
HOLD ON.
WATCH OUT. WATCH OUT.
STILL DOESN'T WORK.
I'M NOT FINISHED.
OH.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]
NICE JOB, JOE.
YOU'RE QUITE
THE CRAFTSMAN.